[{"id": 1649, "question": "Think of London and you're likely to think of the city's famous bright red double-deckers buses. Think of Thailand's capital city, Bangkok, and the noisy tuk-tuk ( ) may come to mind. Picture the American city of San Francisco and you might see the city's trolleybuses. Imagining what these cities would look like without their red buses, tuk-tuks or trolleybuses is difficult. They are symbols of these cities that make them different from anywhere else in the world. However, these city symbols, which are so loved by tourists, are not always so well loved by their city leaders. City leaders want what is best for their city, which often means the most modern transport. In Thailand, Bangkok city authorities have forbidden new tuk-tuks because they consider them noisy and polluting. However, the...\n\nQ: Bangkok's ban on tul-tuks is unsuccessful due to   _  .", "options": ["people's unawareness of environmental protection", "tourists' preference for tuk-tuks over taxis", "the lack of severe punishment for violation", "Locals' willingness to take the tuk-tuks"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2394, "question": "There's a guy like me in every state and federal prison in America,I guess--I'm the guy who can get these for you:cigarettes,a bag of cigar,if you want that,a bottle of wine to celebrate your son or daughter's high school graduation,or almost anything else...within reason,that is.It wasn't always that way. I came to Shawshank when I was just twenty,and I am one of the few people in the prison who is willing to admit what he did.I committed murder.I put a large insurance policy on my wife,who was three years older than 1 was,and then I fixed the brakes of the car her father had given us as a wedding present.It worked out exactly as I had planned,except I hadn't planned on her stopping to pick up the neighbour woman and the woman's son on the way down Castle Hill and into town.The brakes let...\n\nQ: What do we know about the man from the passage?", "options": ["He is treated unfairly in the prison.", "He is in charge of the federal prison.", "He is quite an able person as a prisoner.", "He is the most powerful man in the prison."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 106, "question": "Ariau Amazon Towers The Ariau Amazon Towers hotel lets you sleep in a tree house. Eight towers make up this hotel that offers over 300 rooms. If you really want to get into the spirit, book the Tarzan Suite which is large enough for a big family. You'll be thirty feet up in the air and can travel between the towers through their wooden walkways. Prices: starting at $300 one night for each person for a regular room and going all the way up to $3000 for the Tarzan Suite. For more information, visit the website: http://www.ariautowers.com The Ice Hotel Every winter in Jukkasjarvi, Sweden, a special kind of hotel called the Ice Hotel is built. Each year, world-famous artists are invited to design and produce works of art from the ice, many of which can be found in the rooms. You'll have your c...\n\nQ: What is special about the Ariau Amazon Towers hotel?", "options": ["You can sleep in tree houses.", "You can choose any of the towers.", "It is designed for big families.", "Every room has a walkway."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2346, "question": "Many people keep the stamps in a drawer at home because they'll never know when they might need them! The trouble is that they have no idea of how many stamps they have left. When they want to send something by post, it's very annoying to find out that they have run out of stamps! The Internet is possible to solve the problem. The United States Postal Service has come up with a system which allows people to print their own postage stamps at their own home! This is the perfect solution for those people that have busy lives! Whenever you go to the post office to buy a stamp, you are buying a boring and standard postage stamp. They are red in color, and you can easily buy them on the Internet as well. For example, you can just order a regular 1st class stamp and then print it off using your o...\n\nQ: The problem of keeping stamps at home is that   _  .", "options": ["the stamps may lose color", "you may not find them anywhere", "the stamps may be out of date", "you do not know how many are left"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 924, "question": "In ancient Egypt, a shopkeeper discovered that he could attract customers to his shop simply by making changes to its environment. Modern businesses have been following his lead,with more tactics . One tactic involves where to display the goods. Foe example, stores place fruits and vegetables in the first section. They know that customers who buy the healthy food first will feel happy so that they will buy more junk food later in their trip. In department stores, section is generally next to the women's cosmetics section:while the shop assistant is going back to find the right size shoe, bored customers are likely to wander over cosmetics they might want to try later. Besides, businesses seek to appeal to customers' senses. Stores notice that the smell of baked goods encourages shopping, t...\n\nQ: What is the California builder's story intended to prove?", "options": ["The house structure is a key factor customers consider.", "The more costly the house is, the better it sells.", "An ocean view is much to the customers' taste.", "A good first impression increases sales."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1581, "question": "On a hot summer day, a soft drink can really take away your thirst. At home, at school, in the park or at the movies---you can find one almost anywhere. Carbonated You can see bubbles in these! Of all soft drinks sold, about 75 percent are carbonated . But be careful, carbonated soft drinks have lots of sugar and caffeine . Caffeine is not very good for you in the summer because it takes water out of your body. And the sugar can make you overweight if you drink too much. Fruit juice There are different kinds of juice. One kind is made only from fresh fruit. This kind of fruit juice may not taste sweet enough for some people, but it is nutritious . Another kind of fruit juice tastes good but has lots of sugar in it. Many young people buy this kind because the advertisements are good. It is ...\n\nQ: The writer wrote this passage to  _  .", "options": ["warn us to keep away from soft drinks", "teach us some useful ways of keeping healthy", "tell us how to choose a good one from all kinds of drinks", "make the advertisements for soft drinks"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3412, "question": "Welcome to Arundel Castle which is situated in West Sussex, England. The castle has a history of nearly 1000 years and has welcomed visitors traveling from all over the world. Arundel Castle also plays a starring role in many films. _ The White Garden is planted with soft white Iceberg Roses, and Snow White Lilies. The Rose Garden is newly planted with lovely old-fashioned English roses that are at their very best in June and July. The Organic Kitchen Garden produces a wide range of seasonal fruit and vegetables, pears, cherries and apples. _ In the Castle Shop, you will discover a wide and interesting range of gift ideas for everyone. It offers gifts and souvenirs designed to appeal to all tastes and pockets. Foods, china, books, and stationery are all available. Many are sold in this Cas...\n\nQ: When visiting the castle, you can  _  .", "options": ["get old-fashioned English roses as gifts", "buy eco-friendly products in the Castle Shop", "get seasonal fruit and vegetables for free", "see how the local gifts are being made"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1684, "question": "Americans often say that there are only two things a person can be sure of:death and taxes.Many people feel that the United States has the worst taxes in the world. Taxes are the money that people pay to support their government.There are generally three levels of government in the United States:federal,state,and city;therefore,there are three types of taxes. Salaried people who can earn more than four to five thousand dollars per year must pay a certain part.It depends on their salaries.The federal government has a two-level income tax:that is,15 or 28 percent.$17 850 is the cut off.The tax rate is 15 percent below $17 850 and 28 percent above. The second tax is for the state government:New York,California,or any of the other forty-eight states.Some states have an income tax similar to th...\n\nQ: In the United States,taxes are collected to provide revenues for    .", "options": ["the federal government", "the state government", "the city government", "the three levels of government"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2710, "question": "The word proactivity is fairly common in management literature, but you won't find it in the dictionary. It means that as a human being you take responsibility for your own life. Look at the word responsibility: ability to choose your response, response-ability. Effective people are proactive because they take responsibility. Their behavior is a product of their own decisions, based on values, rather than being a product of their own conditions, based on feelings.For instance, you are planning a picnic with your family.You're excited.You have all the preparations.You've decided where to go, and then it becomes stormy, killing your plan.Proactive people . They realize what their purpose really was, and they creatively have a picnic elsewhere even if it's in their own basement with some spec...\n\nQ: It can be concluded from the passage that determinists      _   .", "options": ["accept things passively", "are in charge of themselves", "are similar to proactive people", "respond to outside conditions actively"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 419, "question": "The day the letter arrived from my university telling me how much I owed them for my first semester, I felt a lump forming in my throat. I hadn't even started my degree and already I was in debt. But although the sum was unsettling, I had peace of mind: I had taken out a loan that would cover the next three years of tuition fees and living expenses. A government body in the UK, the Student Loans Company, provides loans to students whose parents cannot afford to cover the costs themselves. Students forward this amount to the university in advance and agree to repay the loan when they begin their first job. For me, it was a lot of money -around &6,000(60,860 Yuan) per year in total -and much more than I had ever been responsible for. I would receive a couple of thousand pounds per semester -...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements about the loan is right?", "options": ["It's meant for excellent students.", "It's well beyond what the author could be responsible for.", "Students must pay it off as soon as they get a job.", "Students can receive the money monthly."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 814, "question": "Have you heard of the scandal that happened in one of Great Britain's biggest supermarket chains called Tesco? The British love Tesco as it sells very cheap products and it can be found on almost every corner of a British city or town. On January 15th 2013 food inspectors discovered 30 % horsemeat in a certain brand of frozen beefburgers that were mostly sold by Tesco in the UK and Ireland. In times of social media like Facebook and Twitter the news has spread fast and customers have been very concerned about what the food they buy actually contains. Tesco said it had taken away the burgers from the shop shelves immediately, and apologized to their customers. They also promised that they would find out what exactly happened and that they would work harder than ever so this would never happ...\n\nQ: Which statement isn't among the reasons why customers are furious?", "options": ["People trusted Tesco so much that they never expected a scandal like this.", "Everyone can call himself or herself a horse lover in the UK.", "Sellers shouldn't cheat customers.", "The horse is humans' friend."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 273, "question": "Coral reefs are not just beautiful to look at,but also very useful.They shelter nearly 25% of ocean life and provide food for billions of people.However, like many other species,this amazing ecosystem is in danger of dying out! There are two main reasons for the destruction--the rising carbon dioxide levels caused by global warming as well as human influences like bottom operation.While not much can be done about the former,the loss caused by the latter can be reduced. Bottom operation involves dropping nets to the ocean bed and then dragging them up when filled with fish.This action damaged the ocean floor,causing the coral branches to separate from the reefs.While that is very discouraging,the good news is that if these branches are found quickly,they can be saved.At present,that work is...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["bottom operation has affected most underwater creatures", "broken branches of coral can regrow if saved in time", "hundreds of the coralbots have worked well in the oceans", "with the coralbots all damaged coral reefs can be restored"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1507, "question": "Since my son is getting ready for first grade, I asked a friend where she shops for school supplies. For price and convenience, she had a quick answer: schoolpak.com. Parents can buy items or packaged equipment for all grades. The Generic Elementary School-pak for first through fifth graders, for example, is $23.28. (Teachers can also e-mail their grade's or school's whole list for a price on customized kits . Shipping is free for 75 or more kits) _ Teachers thinks highly of educationalwarehouse.com for its learning tools and games--everything from puzzles and puppets to software and chalks.Classroomdirect.com has great prices on over 10.000 products and a special corner offering even deeper discounts. Pick your lunch box The second-most-difficult back-to-school decision, right after what ...\n\nQ: If you want to sell the bikes your children don't use, you can go to   _  .", "options": ["educationalwarehouse.com", "playitagainsports.com", "Feedthepig.org", "Taxadmin.org"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2688, "question": "Silk production has a long and colourful history unknown to most people. Scientific discoveries have shown that silk production existed in China from around 2500 B.C., although it could be much older. For hundreds of years, China kept the secret of silk to itself as one for the most closely protected secrets in history. Anyone revealing the secret of silkworms or trying to take silkworm eggs out of ancient China was punished by death. At one time silk was reserved only for the Chinese emperor. Gradually, others began wearing silk. In addition to being used for clothing, silk came to have industrial uses in ancient China, something that happened in the West only in modern times. Silk was used to make musical instruments, fishing lines, weapons, ropes and even paper. During the Han Dynasty s...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true about the Silk Road?", "options": ["It allowed for economic and cultural exchanges between countries.", "It made China the most powerful country in the ancient world.", "It could only be completed by travellers with access to a boat.", "It was first developed for transferring religious ideas."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1789, "question": "It's wonderful to go to another country, complete a volunteer project and feel that you really have a positive influence. But how can you become an international volunteer? * Plan practically. Contact the organization a few months before leaving and find out if there are materials which are rare and hard to attain for the project. What you often consider plentiful here, such as nails or hammers, is in great need in other parts of the world. * Do the project together, not on your own. You are a guest in the community. The most successful result is not that you build something and walk away, but that you and the community build something as a team. Share skills and build together. * Be flexible. Not everything is going to happen as planned. Often the other country doesn't have the right tool...\n\nQ: When you volunteer to join in a project, you are advised to  _  .", "options": ["build something and walk away", "make good preparation in advance", "avoid involving locals in activities", "depend on yourself to solve problems"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2258, "question": "To me, the ocean is our greatest wilderness. I love swimming in it , surfing its waves, watching it from shore and thinking about all the life living unseen under the surface. When I take my little kids to check out tide pools, we're overjoyed when we find a sea star or some shellfish. Lately, though, I've noticed a change in my favorite pools: there are more sea grasses and fewer animals with shells. I can't help feeling these small changes _ something more troubling about our oceans. It matches what scientists are telling us: our oceans are being troubled by carbon dioxide that threatens corals, colorful fish, salmon, sea otters, even whales. Our oceans are facing a major change. Every hour, a million tons of carbon dioxide from cars, factories and power plants rain down on the world's o...\n\nQ: What is the main purpose of the text ?", "options": ["To inform.", "To educate.", "To persuade .", "To instruct."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1229, "question": "A Russian,a Cuban,an American businessman and an American lawyer were on a train traveling across England. The Russian took out a large bottle of vodka, gave each of the men a drink and then threw the rest half bottle of vodka out of the window. \"Why did you do that?\" asked the American businessman. \"There's too much vodka in my country,\" said the Russian,\"And really we have more than we will ever use.\" A little later,the Cuban passed around fine Havana Cigars. Then he threw his out of the window. \"I thought Cuba is not a rich country,\" the businessman said. \"But you threw that very good cigars out of the window!\" \"Cigars,\" the Cuban answered,\"are the cheapest in my country. We have more of them than we know what to do with.\" The American businessman sat quietly for a moment. Then he got u...\n\nQ: Which do you think is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Traveling across England", "Four Rich Men", "You're Wasting Too Much", "There's Too Much"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1397, "question": "An air of anxious uncertainty spread throughout the small Indian camp as the sun dawned that morning. Some braves gathered beside a smoking campfire. Murmuring sounds could be heard as they talked quietly. Women nervously performed their domestic tasks, preparing a small meal. Several sad, old men sat mute, their morale very low. The camp was pitched at the edge of a deep valley--so deep that one could barely see the calm water at the bottom. The Indians had been taken by surprise and were surrounded and attacked by enemy forces. They fought bravely, but they were degraded by defeat. Their homes were destroyed. Those who had survived had been pursued by the enemy. The chase had lasted for days. Persuaded by their leaders to press on, they had made a wrong turn. Their _ journey ended at the...\n\nQ: Faced with the desperate situation, some Indians in the camp   _  .", "options": ["tried to persuade their leaders to give in to the enemies.", "were still as cheerful as before.", "still remained fearless and loyal to their leaders.", "were in very low spirits."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3035, "question": "Are you a big fan of pirate stories? Do you know how to talk like a pirate? You can have fun on September 19th. This special holiday is called International Talk Like A Pirate Day. It was invented in 1995 by two young Americans, John Baur and Mark Summers. These two good friends came up with this idea when they were playing racquetball, and began to talk like pirates. At that moment, they thought, \"Young people are interested in pirate, but there is no such a chance for people to get together to share it. Why not have a day when everybody talks like a pirate?\" They decided to make September 19th the date. Since then, Baur and Summers have tried hard to promote Talk Like A Pirate Day. As Baur said, \"We've talked like pirates, and encouraged several of our friends to do so every September 19...\n\nQ: Which of the following can serve as the best title of the passage in a newspaper?", "options": ["Young people's pirate dream", "Can you talk like a pirate?", "John Baur and Mark Summers", "September 19th--a traditional day in honor of pirates"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1744, "question": "\"Colour\" and \"color1\" , \"favourite\" and \"favorite\"\"- Have you ever wondered why Americans spell those words without a \"u\"? Is it because they are lazy? Of course not.In fact, the difference in spelling was created by Noah Webster(1758--1843) .He is a teacher who reformed English to make American identity stronger.Linguists celebrated his 250th birthday on October 16,2008.After the Revolutionary War(1775--1783) , Webster believed that Americans should have their own dictionary, rather than rely on British versions.He dropped the British \"u\" in some words.And he changed \"centre\" into \"center\" for children to learn English by spelling words more like they sounded. Webster wasn't shy about expressing his opinions.In defining preposterous (unreasonable) , he wrote: \"A Republican government in t...\n\nQ: Why did Noah Webster create these differences in his dictionary?", "options": ["Because he wanted to make English simple and easy.", "Because he wanted American English to have its own characteristics.", "Because he wanted to achieve political freedom.", "Because he wanted to show that the USA is stronger than the UK."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 691, "question": "Woody Guthrie left California for New York in 1940. There he met Alan Lomax, an expert on America's traditional music. He collected and recorded traditional American folk music, which had few fans at that time. When he heard Woody sing, Lomax knew he had found a true singer of American folk music. Lomax recorded many of Woody's songs for the Library of Congress. Three years later, Woody published a book called Bound for Glory. It was about his early life and travels. From this book people came to learn how Woody had spent his unhappy youth. His mother, Nora Guthrie, died of Huntington's Disease in 1929 when he was only seventeen years old. There was no treatment for the disease. About twenty years later, the disease also began to attack the son. Woody's health got worse and worse, and fina...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true about Huntington's Disease?", "options": ["It killed Woody's mother.", "It was the cause of Woody's death.", "Woody suffered from it all his life.", "It was a deadly disease."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 669, "question": "Since people first sent rockets into space in the 1950s, we have been leaving behind all sorts of things. Some of them, like the camera, were lost by astronauts while they did work outside their spaceship. But much of the space junk is made up of little pieces of things that were once bigger objects, until they struck each other and broke apart. Some things we send into space fall back toward the earth and burn up in the atmosphere. But larger pieces sometimes survive the extreme heat and hit the ground or the ocean at great speeds. So there is always concern that something may fall from the sky and do some harm. But space junk falling on housetops is not the biggest worry. Scientists are concerned about what happens when an empty rocket strikes another while orbiting the earth. Two big th...\n\nQ: Scientists are most worried that the space junk   _  .", "options": ["will stop the future space vehicles", "will do harm to the atmosphere", "will fall on the housetops", "will burn up in space"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1166, "question": "Eva Mozes Kor has good reasons to look down upon Oskar Groning. When she and her twin sister, Miriam, arrived in the Auschwitz death camp, they were met by Josef Mengele and became part of the cruel scientist's experiments. Groning was a junior squad leader at the camp. While Groning could argue he was not directly responsible for procedures carried out on twins,nor for the mass murder of so many others, he played a critical role in the effort to kill Jews. After the war Groning led an ordinary, quiet life until he became alarmed by the rise of Holocaust deniers. He went public with his role and in September 2014 was charged as an accessory to murder. When Groning went on trial in April 2015, Eva Mozes Kor was called as a witness. After her session, she walked straight up to the 93-year-ol...\n\nQ: At the camp, Groning   _            .", "options": ["killed many Jews directly", "treated Eva Mozes Kor badly", "experimented on Eva Mozes Kor", "contributed to killing more Jews"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2665, "question": "Try imagining what the world will be like in the year 3000. Some serious thinkers are starting to imagine just that. Bart: I don't know that present-day electronic chips are, but some sort of chips -- I'd guess maybe plastic. Our three-pound brain is definitely a wonder, perhaps the greatest wonder of natural biology. In this coming century, we'll be re-engineering the brain a piece at a time, first with implants and finally engineering an complete replacement. There's no question that in the distant future we'll play the music of the mind on instruments different from the current ones. So, yes, chips are our destiny . Edward: In 3000 perhaps the biggest difference from today is that there will be no more men. Females can have female children, without any need for men. In about ten years, ...\n\nQ: According to Greg, Heaven in the future is a place where   _  .", "options": ["your scientific idea exists", "you have once traveled", "your own thought travels", "your material world is formed"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3174, "question": "My student teaching experience was a wonderful adventure. I had to deal with various discipline and behavior challenges that occurred again and again. The greatest part of it was the relationship I developed with two students. One of the students was named Michael,whom I met when I was working for a kindergarten. Before I became a morning bus assistant, I'd heard that Michael was a challenging student who would always shout, stand up on the bus, make fun of other students, and distract bus driver. So I decided that each morning, when he got on the bus, I'd have Michael sit beside me. At first he didn't like this idea and pouted about it. But soon he settled down, knowing he had no choice. I began to talk to him about little things outside of school life, such as his weekend activities and ...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the text?", "options": ["Selfless giving is always a pleasure for a teacher.", "An act of kindness could bring the students great joy.", "Different students should be taught in different ways.", "Students should learn to appreciate teachers' concern."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1796, "question": "By teaching your children fire safety you can make sure they know what to do when a house fire occurs. Making sure that your children know exactly what is required of them cuts down on the chaos of the emergency situation and helps keep your family safe and secure. Make sure your children know how to correctly stop, drop, and roll and feel confident in the fact that it works. It puts out the flames. The usual response to clothing catching on fire is to run around and run about wildly, which only exposes the fire to more oxygen and feeds the flames. Your children should also know to touch door handles before opening the door to see if they are hot. If they are, it means that there's a fire in the next room, and they should leave the door closed and find another route out of the house. Make ...\n\nQ: What should children do when their clothing catches on fire?", "options": ["Stop, drop and roll without delay", "Run around quickly to put out the flames.", "Call the firefighter for help at once.", "Feel confident and don't be afraid of fire."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2949, "question": "Animals can be extremely protective of their young. But when hard times call, animal fathers can be really a danger to their own kids. Daddy Lion A combination of laziness, pride, cruelty and anger makes the lion one of the most fearsome and worst dads of the animal kingdom. When not walking proudly across the jungle, the father lion just lazes around under the sun, or waits for one of its lioness partners to bring back food. Once the lioness gets home the food, the lion eats up most of it, and leaves little or nothing at all for the kids. The father doesn't even train the kids for hunting and surviving, it is the lioness who teaches them how to _ themselves. The Polar Father Cute, pure and soft. Protective of young ones and family? Sure. But what makes the polar bears one of the worst dad...\n\nQ: Which can best describe the male assassin bug?", "options": ["Weak but kind.", "Responsible and careful.", "Strong and cruel.", "Little but cruel."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2941, "question": "Although most weddings follow long-held traditions, there's still room for American individualism. For example, the usual place for a wedding is in a church. But some people get married outdoors in a scenic spot. A few even have the ceremony while skydiving or riding on horseback! The couple may invite hundreds of people or just a few close friends. They choose their own style of colors, decorations and music during the ceremony. But some things rarely change. The bride usually wears a beautiful long white wedding dress. She traditionally wears \"something old, something new, something borrowed and something blue.\" The groom wears a formal suit. Several close friends participate in the ceremony as attendants, including the best man and the maid of honor. As the ceremony begins, the groom an...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from the passage?", "options": ["Wedding vows are usually composed by the minister.", "The young couple face the audience throughout the wedding.", "The couple composes their own vows to avoid nervousness.", "The minister is the chief witness at the wedding ceremony"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1361, "question": "Never before in Chinese history has a documentary film aroused so much public enthusiasm. Everybody is talking about a new 7-part documentary called A Bite of China which was recently broadcast late at night on CCTV I. The documentary describes various _ across the vast Chinese culinary landscape. According to Taobao, China's biggest online retail website, just five days after the series began to air, nearly 6 million people went to the site in search of various local specialties, particularly those mentioned in the documentary. More than 7.2 million deals were concluded. A ham producer from Yunnan Province saw his sales grow 17-fold in five days. However, one can't help but believe that the documentary's popularity is probably linked to the endless stream of terrible food security issues ...\n\nQ: We can infer from what a netizen wrote in one well -received article that   _  .", "options": ["none of the television viewers have a knowledge of the Chinese food culture", "there is a huge contrast between the ancient food culture and the reality", "the price of food is too high for many common people", "the documentary was made by a world-famous Chinese director"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2094, "question": "When George was thirty-five, he bought a small plane and learned to fly it. He soon became very good and made his plane do all kinds of tricks . George had a friend, whose name was Mark. One day George offered to take Mark up in his plane. Mark thought, \" I've traveled in a big plane several times, but I've never been in a small one, so I'll go. \" They went up, and George flew around for half an hour and did all kinds of tricks in the air. When they came down again, Mark was glad to be back safely, and he said to his friend in a shaking voice, \"Well , George, thank you very much for those two trips in your plane.\" George was very surprised and said, \" Two trips? \" \" Yes, my first and my last. \" answered Mark....\n\nQ: Mark went up in George's plane   _  .", "options": ["twice", "only once", "several times", "once or twice"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1310, "question": "History is full of cases where dreams have been a pathway to creativity and discovery. A striking example is provided by Dr. Otto Loewi, a pharmacologist and winner of a Nobel Prize. Loewi had spent years studying the chemical transmission of nerve impulses . A major breakthrough in his research came when he dreamed of an experiment three nights in a row. On the first two nights he woke up and wrote down the experiment quickly and untidily on paper. But the next morning, he couldn't tell what the notes meant. On the third night, he got up after having the dream. This time, instead of making notes he went straight to his laboratory and performed the important experiment. Loewi later said that if the experiment had occurred to him while awake he would not have given it another thought. Loewi...\n\nQ: The author probably thinks that   _  .", "options": ["Loewi should not have done his experiment", "dreaming is of very little value to most people", "college students should not try out dream experiments", "nervous feelings may stop someone thinking of useful ideas"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1209, "question": "For almost two months Dominic York, a 23-year-old hairdresser, wandered about hospitals all night, wearing a white coat and pretending he was a doctor. Yesterday he proudly claimed in court that despite his complete lack of medical experience or qualifications, he had saved several people's lives. He had even been allowed to assist a surgeon during an emergency operation on a patient who was about to die on something she had swallowed. \"I watched one of those TV dramas about a hospital and suddenly I felt like playing one of the roles myself. So I put on a white jacket and a stethoscope and walked around one of the biggest hospital in London. At first I just watched. Once you learn how doctors talk to patients, nurses and others doctors, it's easy to take people in,\" he said. One of the pa...\n\nQ: York was proud of the fact that    _   .", "options": ["a surgeon let him watch an operation.", "he could perform some duties of a doctor", "he had cheated doctors for so long", "people thought he could become a real doctor"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2353, "question": "Centerville High School Essay Contest \"Write All About It\" Calling All Aspiring Authors--Centerville High School Essay Contest *Rules 1.Students are asked to present essays of 500 to 700 words of their own work. Any essay containing material plagiarized from another source will be disqualified . 2.Manuscripts should be typed double-spaced,with the student's name,address,and grade level on a separate sheet of paper. 3.Essays must be turned in by 4:00 p.m. on November 30.They can be brought to Mrs. Elton in Rom 104 or to Mr. Markham in the school library. *Essay-Writing Tips 1.Catch your readers' interests--Your opening should immediately pull your readers into your essay. Asking a question or starting with an story,quotation,or surprising statement is a good way to do this. 2.Create a pictu...\n\nQ: What do we know by inference from the passage?", "options": ["The computer lab usually closes at 4:15 p.m. each day.", "Winning essays will be published in the Centerville Times.", "Every contestant will benefit from the essay contest.", "The essay contest is held annually at Centerville High School."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1856, "question": "A rainforest is an area covered by tall trees with the total high rainfall spreading quite equally through the year and the temperature rarely dipping below l6degC. Rainforests have a great effect on the world environment because they can take in heat from the sun and adjust the climate. Without the forest cover,these areas would reflect more heat into the atmosphere, warming the rest of the world. Losing the rainforests may also influence wind and rainfall patterns,potentially causing certain natural disasters all over the world. In the past hundred years,humans have begun destroying rainforests in search of three major resources : land for crops,wood for paper and other products,land for raising farm animals. This action affects the environment as a whole. For example,a lot of carbon dio...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the text that   _  .", "options": ["we can get enough resources without rainforests", "there is great medicine potential in rainforests", "we will grow fewer kinds of crops in the gained land", "the level of annual rainfall affects wind patterns"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 734, "question": "Vampires , creatures of myth, have been around in one form or another for centuries. Terrifying but also attractive, they are as popular in the early 21st century as ever, as the current popularity of Twilight series, and its hero Edward Cullen, show. Vampires first appeared in fiction in the 1700s; in 1895 Irish novelist Bram Stoker published Dracula, introducing the world's most famous vampire. But just what is it about these drinkers of human blood that continues to fascinate us? Speaking to Eric Lewis of the Times and Transcript website, academic Deborah Wells said that vampires are \"culturally adaptive \". \"We create very different vampires to fit different times. Edward Cullen is not the same as Count Dracula,\" she said. Different as they are, Wells believes vampires are \"the perfect ...\n\nQ: The main idea of this passage should be   _  .", "options": ["Why Twilight is so popular nowadays", "Vampires have been around us for long", "Vampires may continue to drink our blood", "We still like the story about vampires"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1029, "question": "Some kinds of mental skills naturally decrease as people get older. Yet research seems to show that some training can improve such skills. A recently published study also appears to demonstrate that the good effects of training can last for many years after that training has ended. Researchers at Johns Hopkins University in Maryland wanted to learn how long memory and thinking skills would last in older people who trained to keep them. The people were part of the ten-year research project. They were taught methods meant to improve their memory, thinking and ability to perform everyday tasks. More than 2,800 volunteered for the study called ACTIVE - short for Advanced (Cognitive) Training for Independent and Vital Elderly. Most studied when they were more than 70 years old. The volunteers t...\n\nQ: Which statement is true according to the text?", "options": ["This kind of training can only have effect on people for a few years.", "The people were trained during a period of ten years.", "All the people who were studied were more than 70 years old.", "The second group were trained how to remember word lists."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1135, "question": "The slogan \"a dog is for life, not just for Christmas\" has been going strong for 27 years now. Dogs and cats have been popular Christmas gifts in the gifts in the UK and Europe for many years. But some people still haven't quite got the message. The slogan still holds good. Some 105,000 dogs were _ by local government last year because they had been abandoned, many of them shortly after the festival season. The main reason given by owners for handing their dogs over to the Dogs Trust is that the dogs need more attention than they can give; behavioral problems and moving home are also reasons given. But Eleanor Silk, the Trust's communications director, says, \"It's often four or five months after Christmas, in early summer, when owners find that the dog has got too big and too active, or it...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is NOT a reason for pets to be abandoned?", "options": ["Pets spread some diseases.", "Pets damage some things in the house.", "The owners can't take good care of the pets.", "The owners have to move to other places."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 125, "question": "Three Central Texas men were honored with the Texas Department of Public Safety's Director's Award in a Tuesday morning ceremony for their heroism in saving the victims of a fiery two car accident. The accident occurred on March 25 when a vehicle lost control while traveling on a rain-soaked State Highway 6 near Baylor Camp Road. It ran into an oncoming vehicle, leaving the occupants trapped inside as both vehicles burst into flames. Bonge was the first on the scene and heard children screaming. He broke through a back window and pulled Mallory Smith, 10, and her sister, Megan Smith,9,from the wreckage. The girls' mother, Beckie Smith, was not with them at the time of the wreck, as they were traveling with their baby sitter, Lisa Bow bin. Beckie Smith still remembers the sickening feeling ...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be used to describe Bozeman?", "options": ["Kind.", "Modest.", "Excited.", "Smart."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1878, "question": "Melissa Poe was 9 years old when she began a campaign for a cleaner environment by writing a letter to the then President Bush. Through her on efforts, her letter was reproduced on over 250 donated billboards across the country. The response to her request for help was so huge that Poe established Kids For A Cleaner Environment (Kids F.A.C.E.) in 1989. There are now 300,000 members of Kids F.A.C.E. worldwide and it is the world's largest youth environmental organization. Poe has also asked the National Park Service to carry out a \"Children's Forest\" project in every national park. In 1992, she was invited one of only six children in the world to speak at the Earth Summit in prefix = st1 /Brazilas part of the Voices of the future Program. In 1993, she was given a Caring Award for her effort...\n\nQ: Kids F.A.C.E. is   _  .", "options": ["a program to help students with writing", "a project of litter recycling", "a campaign launched by President Bush", "a club of environmental protection"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1479, "question": "A person named Bernard Jackson today is a free man, but he has many bitter memories. He spent five years in prison after a jury wrongly convicted (...) him of raping two women. At Jackson's trial, although two witnesses testified that Jackson was with them in another location at the time of the crime, he was convicted anyway. Why? The jury believed the testimony of the two victims, who positively identified Jackson as the man who had attacked them. The court eventually freed Jackson after the police found the real criminal. Many factors influence the accuracy of eyewitness testimony. For instance, witnesses sometimes see photographs of several suspects before they try to identify the person they saw in a group of people. They can become confused by seeing many photographs of similar faces....\n\nQ: An inaccurate eyewitness testimony may lead to   _   .", "options": ["the misunderstanding of the case", "the disbelief in the court", "the disrespect for the eyewitness", "the conviction of an innocent person"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 210, "question": "On a small farm in Mexico, there are no schools. A bus is the school! The driver of the bus is the teacher! It is a school bus, but it doesn't take children to school. It just goes round from place to place, and sometimes it comes to this farm. The bus will stay here for three months. The farmers call it a school on wheels . Every time the bus comes, the farmers come running to it, shouting and laughing. They warmly welcome the school bus! When the bus is on the farm, in the morning, the teacher teaches the small children. In the afternoon, the bigger children come to have their lessons because they must work in the morning. At night, the fathers and mothers come to school. They want to learn, too. How the farmers hope that some day they can have a real school on their farm!...\n\nQ: .  The bus school will   _  .", "options": ["take children to school", "stay there for lunch", "take the fathers and mothers to school", "go round from place to place"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 650, "question": "Lee Ann Laraway has polio and is not able to move very much. Most things are out of reach for her. Jeannie, a Labrador retriever, acts as her arms and legs. Jeannie understands 72 or more different commands. On a shopping trip, she can get money for Lee Ann at the bank or candies at the store. She can pay the cashier and get change back. Jeannie brings things to Lee Ann and puts them in her lap. Jeannie was trained at a place called Canine Companions for Independence, located on twelve acres of land in Santa Rosa (California). The land was donated by the cartoonist Charles Shultz. \"We train four different types of dogs here,\" said Ken Kirsh, a dog trainer there. \"Hearing dogs, service dogs, skilled companion dogs, and facility dogs.\" Trainers work with Labrador retrievers and golden retrie...\n\nQ: According to this passage, we can know that Jeannie is Lee Ann's  _  .", "options": ["servant", "daughter", "dog", "mother"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 902, "question": "When Charles Strattion was five, he stopped growing. His mother took him to see the famous showman, P. T. Barnum, and thought a small person would be the perfect addition to his show. He hired Charles' parents along with him, and they traveled around the world together. He gave the two-foot-tall Charles a new name, general Tom Thumb. He taught Tom how to sing, dance, act, and tell jokes. When he felt Tom was ready to perform on stage, he made up ads. To stir up great interest, he said that Tom was eleven years old and had come from England. Tom's act was very popular and brought in a lot of money. By the time Tom was an adult, he had grown very rich. He had become a billionaire at the age of twenty-five. Fortunately for Tom, Mr. Barnum added more little people to his show, and Tom became l...\n\nQ: \"the talk of the town\" means  _  .", "options": ["they were in the newspaper", "people spread many rumors about them", "they were the most popular things happening", "they were discussed in a city meeting"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 626, "question": "British newspapers are among the oldest and most famous in the world. But recently big changes have seen these traditional publications try to fit the modern world. After 221 years, The Times has changed its size to become much smaller. In fact, the paper has cut its size in half from a broadsheet to tabloid . In prefix = st1 /Britainthe newspaper market is divided between the larger broadsheets and the smaller tabloids. These terms refer to the size of the papers' pages but there is also a clear difference in content. Broadsheets such as The Times, the Guardian and Daily Telegraph are serious papers. They cover a broad range of political, economic and international issues. Their stories are also reasonably long and use quite formal language. Tabloids have far more stories about less serio...\n\nQ: Which of the following newspapers would you read if you are interested in lives of film stars?", "options": ["The Sun", "The Times", "The Independent", "The Guardian"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1015, "question": "BEIJING--Seven prestigious universities in China announced Sunday that they would begin using the same independent exam --besides the national one --to test students hoping to gain entrance to them in 2011. The seven are Peking University, Beihang University, Beijing Normal University, Nankai University, Fudan University, Xiamen University and Hong Kong University. Students who want to gain entrance to any of the seven universities will only have to sit one independent exam, according to the joint announcement. \"This will help lighten the students' load, otherwise they must take several exams for different universities ,\"said the announcement. Passing the exam could result in more than one interview chance, giving the students more opportunities to choose their favorite universities. China...\n\nQ: If students pass the independent exam, they will   _  .", "options": ["take the national exam.", "have one or more interview chances.", "be admitted to one of the universities.", "he trained to be adapted to universities life and studies."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3018, "question": "The findings of a new survey have American professors talking about the good old days--when A's were a lot tougher to earn. Sites like Rate My Professors.com make it easy for students to find a class taught by a professor who is known as an \"easy grader\".A recent survey by Kaplan Test Prep found that 46 percent of the more than 1,200 students polled admitted to using the site for just such a purpose. \"Our research shows that many of today's college students are looking at multiple factors when picking out courses: overall teacher quality that will result in a good learning experience, but also instructors who don't like to award a lot of C's and D's,\" said Jeff Olson, vice president of research at Kaplan Test Prep. \"While it makes sense that students would choose kinder graders, it also he...\n\nQ: The passage suggests that    _   .", "options": ["universities will employ hard graders", "if we want to be happy, we should be ignorant", "A's are becoming easy to earn at most US universities", "professors and instructors should give students higher grades"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3356, "question": "Iceland, an island just south of the Arctic Circle, has fairly mild winters, thanks to warm ocean currents. Time your vacation here during the winter months to take advantage of off-season deals. Off-season means good deals on flights, hotels and tours. You may also find that the locals are a bit friendlier and more welcoming when tourists aren't arriving in crowds. In the winter months, there are less than seven hours of daylight; thus, chances are good you'll catch sight of the northern lights. Sunsets are also beautiful at this time, making for some great photo opportunities. In Iceland, winter is the perfect time to hike glaciers, go ice climbing, explore caves made out of hardened lava and much more. One of the most popular activities is off-roading in a specially-equipped \"super jeep...\n\nQ: What is true about the volcanoes of Iceland?", "options": ["The majority of them are quiet.", "Their age hasn't been determined.", "All but one of them are extinct.", "Citizens aren't affected by them."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1532, "question": "Conventional wisdom is a major barrier to innovation that threatens the survival of companies everywhere.It's based on the assumption that old ideas will always work,so they shouldn't be challenged. While this may be a valid assumption in situations that don't change,it's unlikely to hold true in a changing situation.In today's rapid changing global environment,old methods often don't work,and stubbornly using them can lead to major problems. Most people seem to agree with conventional wisdom because it gives one a false sense of security.If everyone else believes it,then it must be true.Individuals who use conventional wisdom are certain that they are right,and being right is good. They want to continue using old ideas rather than take risks with changes that might not work.In 1977,Ken Ol...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly written to tell us that   _  .", "options": ["old methods are changing with time", "opportunities lead to business success", "conventional wisdom limits innovation", "successful companies need wise leaders"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2359, "question": "The crowd cheered and cheered. The man with the horn waved and smiled his great smile. \"More! More!\" cried the crowd. And Louis Armstrong took his horn and began to play again. Here he was in England. Now a famous man, he was rich. He knew many important people. Wherever he went, people knew his name. They wanted to hear his music. As he played the sad, slow songs, Louis thought of his home in New Orleans. He lived there as a boy. It was a busy, exciting city. But Louis's family was very poor. He went to work to help his mother. He also went to school. One of Louis's teachers asked him to join the school band. \"This horn is yours until you leave our school,\" his teacher said. Louis's music was jazz and he loved it. He remembered all the music he heard. He didn't learn to read music until h...\n\nQ: He was famous for   _  .", "options": ["his horn", "his sad songs", "his love for music", "his wonderful jazz music"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 150, "question": "As the train approached the seaside town where I was going to spend my holiday, I went into the corridor to stretch my legs.I stayed there for a short while,breathing in the fresh air and exchanging a few words with one of the passengers,whom I had met earlier on the station platform. When I turned to go back to my seat,I happened to glance into the compartment next to mine.Sitting there was a man who many years before had been my neighbor.He was a great talker, I remembered;it used to take hours to get away from him once he began talking.I was not at all sorry when he went to live in another part of London.We had not met since then,nor did I wish to meet him now, when my holiday was about to begin. Luckily at that moment he was much too busy talking to the man opposite him to have the cha...\n\nQ: The writer went into the corridor because   _  .", "options": ["he wanted to take a rest", "he wanted to meet his friend", "he wanted to get off the train", "he wanted to have a walk"], "answer": 0}]